Local 1199 Photograph Files 5933 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Headquarters' building in progress, 6/1969 (Box 48, Folder 40)
  #1118
- Scholarship Committee, 6/1969 (Box 48, Folder 41)
  #1119
- Clothes for Charleston, 6/1969 (Box 48, Folder 42)
  #1120
- Joe Betancourt, 6/1969 (Box 48, Folder 43)
  #1121
- J.P. Stevens pickets + picketing S. Can. Gov. McNair in N.Y., 6/1969 (Box 48, Folder 44)
  #1122
- K. Griswald Speaks, 6/1969 (Box 48, Folder 45)
  #1123
- Scholarship winners (Garcia, McCludy) (Box 48, Folder 46)
  #1124
- Simon Scher, 7/1969 (Box 48, Folder 47)
  #1125
- Camp Departure, 7/1969 (Box 48, Folder 48)
  #1126
- Boat ride, 7/1969 (Box 48, Folder 49)
  #1127
- Mt. Sinai baby technicians, 8/1969 (Box 48, Folder 50)
  #1128
- Voter registration - Montefiore, 8/1969 (Box 48, Folder 51)
  #1129
- Lenox Hill high noon, 8/1969 (Box 48, Folder 52)
  #1130
- Yeshiver contract ratified, 8/1969 (Box 48, Folder 53)
  #1131
- Elisa Rivera, 8/1969 (Box 48, Folder 54)
  #1132
- Associated Home Victory, 6/1969 (Box 48, Folder 55)
  #1133
- Jamaica HIP lockout, 10/1969 (Box 48, Folder 56)
  #1134
- Knickerbocker "We Care", 10/1969 (Box 48, Folder 57)
  #1135
- Social Work feature, 10/1969 (Box 48, Folder 58)
  #1136
- Peace Action Day Viet War Moratorium, 10/15/1969 (Box 48, Folder 59)
  #1137
- Glotzer mug shot, 10/1969 (Box 48, Folder 60)
  #1138
- Harvey Snyder - Anti-war vet, 10/1969 (Box 48, Folder 61)
  #1139
- Gary Lamson eats fire, 10/1969 (Box 48, Folder 62)
  #1140
- Lincoln Rehab Mobile, 10/1969 (Box 48, Folder 63)
  #1141
- David Ramos - Artist, 10/1969 (Box 48, Folder 64)
  #1142
- Joe James, 10/1969 (Box 48, Folder 65)
  #1143
- Julia Brown (psych. Worker), 10/1969 (Box 48, Folder 66)
  #1144
- Lindsay at Jt. D.A., 10/1969 (Box 48, Folder 67)
  #1145
- Oscar Weiss, 11/1969 (Box 48, Folder 68)
  #1146
- Murray Sharnoff, 11/1969 (Box 48, Folder 69)
  #1147
- Sen. Goodell at labor peace mtg., 11/1969 (Box 48, Folder 70)
  #1148
- Housing Testimony (Turner, Malave), 11/1969 (Box 48, Folder 71)
  #1149
- Fall Dance, 11/1969 (Box 48, Folder 72)
  #1150
- March on Washington (Moratorium), 11/1969 (Box 48, Folder 73)
  #1151
- Brown twins, 11/1969 (Box 48, Folder 74)
  #1152
- Bronx-Leb art show, 11/1969 (Box 48, Folder 75)
  #1153
- Ann Freeman + Mother, 11/1969 (Box 48, Folder 76)
  #1154
- Rocky Demonstration, 11/1969 (Box 48, Folder 77)
  #1155
- Leon Davis, 12/1969 (Box 48, Folder 78)
  #1156
- Doris Turner portraits by Hunstein, 12/1969 (Box 48, Folder 79)
  #1157
- Artists - Keith Lewin, Robert Coran, 12/1969 (Box 48, Folder 80)
  #1158
- Nat'l. Union Hosp. Nursing Home Employees Conference, 12/12-14/1969 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  #1159
- Nat'l. Union Hosp. Nursing Home Employees conference, 12/12-14/1969 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  #1159 (cont.)
- Eloise Moore, 12/1969 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  #1160
- GE picket line of Macy's, 12/1969 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  #1161
- Housing project model, 12/1969 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  #1162
- X-mas party of Clara Maass Workers, 12/1969 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  #1163
- X mas party for kids, NY, 12/1969 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  #1164
- Leon Davis, 12/1969 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  #1165
- Film group, 12/1969 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  #1166
- Simicher Flapan, Israeli speaker, 1/1970 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  #1167
- Rev. Joyce of Charleston, 1/1970 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  #1168
- Staff, Drug, Hosp. Guild, 1/1970 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  #1169
- King Ceremonial Service @ Mt. Sinai, 1/15/1970 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  #1170
- LPN's, technicians discuss contract demands, 1/1970 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  #1171
- Foner Portraits, 2/1970 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  #1172
- Training & Upgrading programs, 12/1969 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  #1173
- N.J. Hospital contract ratify mtg., 12/1969 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  #1174
- Louise Evans - aide of NYU, 1/1970 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  #1175
- Spanish language meeting, 11/1969 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  #1176
- Maimonides delegates Carroll & Dawson, 1/1970 (Box 49, Folder 20)
  #1177
- Softball play, 9/1969 (Box 49, Folder 21)
  #1178
- Grape Boycott support - Chavez speaks, 10/1969 (Box 49, Folder 22)
  #1179
- Mr. & Mrs. S. Cobb retire, 2/1970 (Box 49, Folder 23)
  #1180
- Animal Institute at Einstein, 2/1970 (Box 49, Folder 24)
  #1181
- Spanish Dance, 5/1969 (Box 49, Folder 25)
  #1182
- Delegate graduates, 11/1969 (Box 49, Folder 26)
  #1183
- Baltimore - King visit before Hopkins election, 8/1969 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  #1184
- Juglis House - Philly, 11/1969 (Box 49, Folder 28)
  #1185
- Davis on Barr Gray Show, 2/1970 (Box 49, Folder 29)
  #1186
- ]X-ray students, 2/1970 (Box 49, Folder 30)
  #1187
- Salute to Freedom, New Jersey, 2/1970 (Box 49, Folder 31)
  #1188
- Guild Delegate Assembly (Box 49, Folder 32)
  #1189
- Hartford's Mt. Sinai election, 2/1970 (Box 49, Folder 33)
  #1190
- Delegate banquet, 2/1970 (Box 49, Folder 34)
  #1191
- Arthur Rosenberg, 3/1970 (Box 49, Folder 35)
  #1192
- Lab Techs, 3/1970 (Box 49, Folder 36)
  #1193
- Kings County Research Lab Strike, 3/1970 (Box 49, Folder 37)
  #1194
- CATCH, 3/1970 (Box 49, Folder 38)
  #1195
- Salute to Freedom, 3/1970 (Box 49, Folder 39)
  #1196
- Cornell Students meet 1199 Leaders, 3/1970 (Box 49, Folder 40)
  #1197
- Photographer Steve Murdock, "I am somebody" (movie), Shors of Claire Brown (Box 49, Folder 41)
  #1198
- Connecticut delegate meeting, 3/1970 (Box 49, Folder 42)
  #1200
- Faces of members at march. E & E + St. Barnabas, 3/1970 (Box 49, Folder 43)
  #1201
- Election Board, 4/1970 (Box 49, Folder 44)
  #1202
- Gertrude Francis portrait, 4/1970 (Box 49, Folder 45)
  #1203
- Billy Barkley, 4/1970 (Box 49, Folder 46)
  #1204
- Booth Memorial Election Win, 4/1970 (Box 49, Folder 47)
  #1205
- Davis testimonial, 3/1970 (Box 49, Folder 48)
  #1206
- Public Health Institute Victory, 4/1970 (Box 49, Folder 49)
  #1207
- X-Ray Conference, 4/1970 (Box 49, Folder 50)
  #1208
- Hospital Negotiating Committee, 4/1970 (Box 49, Folder 51)
  #1209
- April 15 Peace demo at Maimonides, 4/1970 (Box 49, Folder 52)
  #1210
- Bernie Hengber, 4/1970 (Box 49, Folder 53)
  #1211
- April 15, "Tax Day", Antiwar Demonstration, 1970 Bryant Park, Shors Eddie Ayasb (Box 49, Folder 54)
  #1212
- Hosp. negotiations begin Apr. 30, 4/30 (Box 49, Folder 55)
  #1213
- Africans in 1199, 5/1970 (Box 49, Folder 56)
  #1214
- We are at Knickerbocker, 4/1970 (Box 49, Folder 57)
  #1215
- Lillian Carter, 5/1970 (Box 49, Folder 58)
  #1216
- Pauther support rally in New Haven, 4/1970 (Box 49, Folder 59)
  #1217
- Retiree's - Guild + Hospital, 5/1970 (Box 49, Folder 60)
  #1218
- Peace demo May 8, Mt. Sinai (Box 49, Folder 61)
  #1219
- Sid Von Luther, 5/1970 (Box 49, Folder 62)
  #1220
- Peace action at Montefiore, 5/1970 (Box 49, Folder 63)
  #1221
- Peter Ogarro, Cafeteria helper at Montefiore, 5/1970 (Box 49, Folder 64)
  #1222
- Juan Evangelista de Jesus of Montefiore Dietary Dept., 5/1970 (Box 49, Folder 65)
  #1223
- Southside delegate at Training Class, 5/1970 (Box 49, Folder 66)
  #1224
- Bertha Davis new retiree from Bx-Leb Hosp., 5/1970 (Box 49, Folder 67)
  #1225
- Workers Portraits holding picket signs, 5/1970 (Box 49, Folder 68)
  #1226
- Installation of Officers delegates, 5/13/1970 (Box 49, Folder 69)
  #1227
- Dayton Workers, 5/1970 (Box 49, Folder 70)
  #1228
- Mural going up in headquarters building, 5/1970 (Box 49, Folder 71)
  #1229
- Negotiations - hospital, 5/1970 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  #1230 (A)
- Hospital wage talks, 5-6/1970 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  #1230 (B)
- Hospital wage talks, 5-6/1970 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  #1230 ( C )
- Hospital wage talks, 5-6/1970 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  #1230 (D)
- Hospital wage talks, Beth-Israel demonstration, Noon-Mon. 29, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  #1230 (E)
- Hospital wage talks, 5-6/1970 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  #1230 (F)
- 11 Negotiations, Crisis hours, 30 June-1 July, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  #1230 (G)
- Negotiations as documented by CBS-TV, 7/21/1970 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  #1230 (H)
- Wedding of Doris Turner + Willie Keyes, 5/14/1970 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  #1231
- Peace sign on building, 5/1970 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  #1232
- Balt. Installations, 5/1970 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  #1233
- Balt members' on job, 5/1970 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  #1234
- Story Brook v. Committee, 5/1970 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  #1235
- Presbyterian SW Committee, 6/1970 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  #1236
- Harlem Rehab. Ctr., 6/1970 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  #1237
- Hahnemann high noon, 6/1970 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  #1238
- Membership mtg., 6/1970 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  #1239
- Hospital Pension Applicants (Box 50, Folder 18)
  #1240
- Leon Davis: Addressing Jewish currents ____, 17 May 1970 (Box 50, Folder 19)
  #1241
- Ruby Collins, Retiree, 7/1970 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  #1242
- Sid Von Luther Portrait, 7/1970 (Box 50, Folder 21)
  #1243
- Elliott Lewkon, 7/1970 (Box 50, Folder 22)
  #1244
- members faces Hosp. - Guild, 7/1970 (Box 50, Folder 23)
  #1245
- ILPA plaque, 7/1970 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  #1246
- Marie Penfornis - Retiree, 7/1970 (Box 50, Folder 25)
  #1247
- Anne Shore, 7/1970 (Box 50, Folder 26)
  #1248
- Aryeh Meier (ACLU) addressing 1199 Retirees (18 June 1970) (Box 50, Folder 27)
  #1249
- Booth Memorial Soul Day, 6/1970 (Box 50, Folder 28)
  #1251
- Boat ride models, 7/1970 (Box 50, Folder 29)
  #1252
- Ivan Baird, 7/1970 (Box 50, Folder 30)
  #1253
- Theater Producer, 8/3/1970 (Box 50, Folder 31)
  #1254
- HIP Strike victory, 8/1970 (Box 50, Folder 32)
  #1255
- Von Lutten & Basil Patterson, 8/1970 (Box 50, Folder 33)
  #1256
- Philly Mtg., 8/1970 (Box 50, Folder 34)
  #1257
- Murdoch, Steve, 8/1970 (Box 50, Folder 35)
  #1258
- Brockton Home Committee, 9/1970 (Box 50, Folder 36)
  #1259
- Leon Key, 9/1970 (Box 50, Folder 37)
  #1260
- Ella Howell w/member, 9/1970 (Box 50, Folder 38)
  #1261
- New Guild Staffers, 9/1970 (Box 50, Folder 39)
  #1262
- Ruth Mitchelson portrait with 1199, 9/1970 (Box 50, Folder 40)
  #1263
- Maryland General Grievance, 9/1970 (Box 50, Folder 41)
  #1264
- Jenkins Memorial delegate (Balt.), 9/1970 (Box 50, Folder 42)
  #1265
- Political candidates at delegate assemblies, 9/1970 (Box 50, Folder 43)
  #1266
- Mary Moultrie of Local 1199B on TV, 9/1970 (Box 50, Folder 44)
  #1267
- Headquarters building, 9/1970 (Box 50, Folder 45)
  #1268
- Jamaica Medieval Group (HIP) Strike taken 9 July 1970 (Box 50, Folder 46)
  #1250
- New building: varied shots of new building, moving, including mural, Sept. 1970 (Box 50, Folder 47)
- Theresa Pharmacy, 9/1970 (Box 50, Folder 48)
  #1269
- Mural on 1199 Headquarters, 9/1970 (Box 50, Folder 49)
  #1270
- Philly Delegate training, 9/1970 (Box 50, Folder 50)
  #1271
- Balt. Nursing home negotiating committee, 10/1970 (Box 50, Folder 51)
  #1272
- P. Mitchell w/Balt. Offices, 10/1970 (Box 50, Folder 52)
  #1273
- Pearl Brown in pants suit, 10/1970 (Box 50, Folder 53)
  #1274
- Balt. Delegate training, 10/1970 (Box 50, Folder 54)
  #1275
- Ramon Malare presents Puerto Rican flood relief fund check, Nov. 18,1970 (Box 50, Folder 55)
  #1276
- Philly filings, Oct. 21, 10/1970 (Box 50, Folder 56)
  #1277
- LPN Training Course, 10/1970 (Box 50, Folder 57)
  #1278
- St. Mary's (Hoboken) ongoing committee, 10/1970 (Box 50, Folder 58)
  #1279
- Boston missing homes strike, 10/1970 (Box 50, Folder 59)
  #1280
- Ann Hollis + children,10/1970 (Box 50, Folder 60)
  #1282
- Milton Elfman, 10/1970 (Box 50, Folder 61)
  #1281
- Benefit plan gives death benefit to member's widow, 10/1970 (Box 50, Folder 63)
  #1283
- Ramon Malare at HOSTOS Community College (Box 50, Folder 64)
  #1284
- Mural on union headquarters (Box 50, Folder 65)
  #1285
- Farm workers rep Jim Drake at Hosp. D.A., 11/1970 (Box 50, Folder 66)
  #1286
- Swedish MP at Hosp. D.A., 11/1970 (Box 50, Folder 67)
  #1287
- Hosp. D.A., 1st. Mtg. in new auditorium, 11/1970 (Box 50, Folder 68)
  #1288
- Drug addiction in hospitals, 11/1970 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  #1289
- Delegate class grads, 11/1970 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  #1290
- Day of Jacob workers tour new bldg., 11/1970 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  #1291
- Eddie Ayash: shots of Eddie Ayash at Bryant Park peace gathering, 30 Oct. 1970 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  #1292 -- 15 April 1970 and at meeting of 1199 Executive Council, 25 Oct. 1970
- Drug contract crisis - delegate assembly meeting, new build., Oct. 1970 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  #1293
- Politics - Candidates (Goldberg, Paterson, Walinksy) at Sept. Delegate Assembly Meetings, Aug. 1970 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  #1294 -- Also Paterson-Von Luther from Aug. 1970
- How it was in hospitals., Aug. 1970 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  #1295 -- Head shots of Joseph H. Bertel; Claudie Lopez; Ellen Williams; Marie Penfonis; Bernest McRae; Ealie Johnson
- 1199 News Staff, Dan North + Elinor Langer, Aug. 1970 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  #1296
- Camp, Summer: Teen age leadership group, including a number of children of 1199ers, meet at Wel-Met headquarters to review last summer's pilot program, 14, Nov. 1970 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  #1297
- PR Trade Unionists visit Davis, 8/1970 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  #1298
- Retirees' square dance, 11/1970 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  #1299
- Roberson tribute, 11/1970 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  #1300
- Joseph Samuels, 11/1970 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  #1301
- Beth Abraham patients peace meeting, 12/1970 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  #1302
- Ambulance driver in Montefiore members sideline, 10/1970 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  #1303
- King bust by Dr. Allan Bleich, 11/1970 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  #1304
- Von Johnson - Hopkins grievance, 12/1970 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  #1305
- Hopkins parking, 12, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  #1306
- LPN Committee, 12/1970 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  #1307
- Chesapeake Manor Strikers, Balt., 12/1970 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  #1308
- Adams House Striker - Conn., 12, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  #1309
- Baltimore delegate training, 12, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  #1310
- Spanish dance, 11/1970 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  #1311
- Visitors from a Jr. High School, 12/1970 (Box 51, Folder 24)
  #1312
- X-ray Committee, 12/1970 (Box 51, Folder 25)
  #1313
- Anibal Garcia of Bronx-Lebanon, 12/1970 (Box 51, Folder 26)
  #1314
- St. Barnabas diet aides, 12/1970 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  #1315
- Alvarez del Vayo, 12/1970 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  #1316
- Benefit Plan gives check to crippled kids + mom, 12/1970 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  #1317
- Pension Ceremony, 12/1970 (Box 51, Folder 30)
  #1318
- Old Marjorie Bond + deleg. Jadonia Dunn of Haym Saloman, 12/1970 (Box 51, Folder 31)
  #1320
- Ben/Catz on Ch. 13 TV, "Free Time", 12/1970 (Box 51, Folder 32)
  #1321
- Boston-Jewish Memorial Committee, 1/1971 (Box 51, Folder 33)
  #1323
- Lewis Hoyte, 1/1971 (Box 51, Folder 34)
  #1324
- Taylor w/African visitor, 1/1971 (Box 51, Folder 35)
  #1325
- TV Set, 1/1971 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  #1327
- McDaniel Ellison, 1/1971 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  #1330
- French back pay, 1/1971 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  #1331
- Social Service Committee (Box 51, Folder 39)
  #1332
- Juan + Helena Farinas, 1/1971 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  #1333
- Southside Hospital, 1/1971 (Box 51, Folder 41)
  #1334
- Baltimore LPNs, 1/1971 (Box 51, Folder 42)
  #1335
- Baltimore Exec. Bd. w/Davis, 1/1971 (Box 51, Folder 43)
  #1336
- Philly rally w/hardy Williams, 1/26/1971 (Box 51, Folder 44)
  #1337
- Armando Ramirez retires, 1/1971 (Box 51, Folder 45)
  #1338
- Rally for Juan Farinias, 1/1971 (Box 51, Folder 46)
  #1339
- Medical panel of Benefit Plan, 1/1971 (Box 51, Folder 47)
  #1340
- Nora Casey Portrait, 1/1971 (Box 51, Folder 48)
  #1341
- Roland Dorsainville, 2/1971 (Box 51, Folder 49)
  #1342
- Security Guard Jim Hodges, 2/1971 (Box 51, Folder 50)
  #1343
- Youth Panelists (Hunstein), Vera Clarke, 2/1971 (Box 51, Folder 51)
  #1344
- Theater 1199, Vinie Burrows, 1/21/1971 (Box 51, Folder 52)
  #1345
- Theater 1199, Vinie Burrows, 1/31/1974, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 53)
  #1345B
- Housewarming of new headquarters, 11/1970 (Box 51, Folder 54)
  #1346
- Dolores Dunbar of Credit Union, 2/1971 (Box 51, Folder 55)
  #1347
- Delegate class advanced, 2/1971 (Box 51, Folder 56)
  #1348
- Morrisiania demonstration, 2/1971 (Box 51, Folder 57)
  #1349
- Area Dance Bronx, 2/13/1971 (Box 51, Folder 58)
  #1350
- Maimonides peace rally, 2/1971 (Box 51, Folder 59)
  #1351
- Brookdale Clericals, 2/1971 (Box 51, Folder 60)
  #1352
- Clive Jenkins with Moe Foner, 2/1971 (Box 51, Folder 61)
  #1353
- Chorus, 2/1971 (Box 51, Folder 62)
  #1354
- Area Dance Brooklyn, 2/1971 (Box 51, Folder 63)
  #1355
- Copy of Malcolm X photo at 1962 hospital org. rally, 2/1971 (Box 51, Folder 64)
  #1356
- Retirees Art Class + Camera Class, 3/1971 (Box 51, Folder 65)
  #1357
- Leonard Woodcock, 3/1971 (Box 51, Folder 66)
  #1358
- Howard Da Silva Theatre 1199, 28 Feb. 1971 (Box 51, Folder 67)
  #1359
- Methadone program of Beth Israel, 3/8-9/1971 (Box 51, Folder 68)
  #1360
- McCoy Jennings, $4,000 bond, 3/1971 (Box 51, Folder 69)
  #1361
- Fordham Technicians Campaign, 3/1971 (Box 51, Folder 70)
  #1362
- March, 1971, Telephone Operators at Union (Box 51, Folder 71)
  #1363
- Stoney Brook V. Cafeteria Strike, 3/1971 (Box 51, Folder 72)
  #1364
- Chorus of 1199, 3/1971 (Box 51, Folder 73)
  #1365
- Philly babies, 3/1971 (Box 51, Folder 74)
  #1366
- Stoney Brook picketing Greyhound, 3/1971 (Box 51, Folder 75)
  #1367
- West Virginia, 3/1971 (Box 51, Folder 76)
  #1368
- Drug delegate class, Nassau-Suffolk, 3/1971 (Box 51, Folder 77)
  #1369
- Hudson Nat'l. ratifies contract, 3/1971 (Box 51, Folder 78)
  #1370
- Guild Delegate Class, 3/1972 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  #1371
- Guild Social Service Committee, 3/1971 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  #1372
- Harlem Prep. Mtg., 3/1971 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  #1373
- Local 1199 Col. Officials, 3/1971 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  #1374
- Spanish Affairs Committee, 4/1971 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  #1375
- March to Wall St., 4/5/1971 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  #1376
- Kingsbrook Peace Rally, 4/6/1971 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  #1377
- Health Care Conference Committee: Committee Planning - 12 June, Conference, 5 April 1971 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  #1378
- LPNs go to Albany, 4/5/1971 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  #1379
- Boston Membership Meeting, 4/14/1971 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  #1380
- Health Systems hearing by Sen. Kennedy Davis testifies, 4/15/1971 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  #1381
- Labor History for 1199 Staff by Phil Foner, 4/1971 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  #1382
- Retirees from Hospitals get first checks, 4/1971 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  #1383
- Teatro 1199, 4/19/1971 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  #1384
- Coretta King in Philly, 4/28/1971 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  #1385
- City Hall Rally against budget cuts, 4/27/1971 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  #1386
- Retiree graduates, 4/1971 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  #1387
- Peace March to Washington, 4/24/1971 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  #1388
- Art Show by Unity Hospital Members, 4/1971 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  #1389
- Lopez, 5/1971 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  #1390
- Housing Site - Cleared, 5/1971 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  #1391
- Davis' Super Drugs Picketed, 5/1971 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  #1392
- Delegates Graduate, 5/1971 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  #1393
- Guild dinner dance, 5/1971 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  #1394
- Guild LPN Committee, 5 May 1971 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  #1395
- Hahnesmann Victory, 5/1971 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  #1396
- California LPNs, 5/1971 (Box 52, Folder 27)
  #1397
- Brookdale LPNs, 5/1971 (Box 52, Folder 28)
  #1398
- Negley House - Pitts, 5/1971 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  #1399
- Visitors from Jr. High School, 5/1971 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  #1400
- Hands, victory symbol (Box 52, Folder 31)
  #1401
- Ruth Bell - LPN, 6/1971 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  #1402
- Wilkes-Barre Rally, 5/1971 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  #1403
- Coretta King Portrait unveiled, 5/1971 (Box 52, Folder 34)
  #1404
- Corey Island kids, 6/1971 (Box 52, Folder 35)
  #1405
- Jim Baykin Portrait, 6/1971 (Box 52, Folder 36)
  #1406
- Ed Bragg Portrait, 6/1971 (Box 52, Folder 37)
  #1407
- Harry Salinsky, 6/1971 (Box 52, Folder 38)
  #1409
- On the job-hospital (Guild, 6/1971 (Box 52, Folder 39)
  #1410
- Spanish members of 1199 in job place or home (Box 52, Folder 40)
  #1411
- Training Program, 6/1971 (Box 52, Folder 41)
  #1412
- Health conference, 6/1971 (Box 52, Folder 42)
  #1413
- Benefit Plan Registration/Lenox Hill, 6/1971 (Box 52, Folder 43)
  #1414
- Philly - Citywide Committee Meeting, 6/1971 (Box 52, Folder 44)
  #1415
- Henry Nicholas, 6/1971 (Box 52, Folder 45)
  #1416
- Baltimore Benefit Plan New Office, 6/16/1971 (Box 52, Folder 46)
  #1417
- Gallery 1199 Opening, 22 June 1971 (Box 52, Folder 47)
  #1420
- Medicenter Strike, 6/1971 (Box 52, Folder 48)
  #1421
- Retiree Max Hertzoff, 1/1971 (Box 52, Folder 49)
  #1422
- Hillude SW Negotiations, 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 50)
  #1423
- Visiting Turks, 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 51)
  #1424
- Ronnie Dyson (Box 52, Folder 52)
  #1425
- Roy Butler, 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 53)
  #1426
- Art Show quotes, Hosp. Div. Members + Guild, 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 54)
  #1427
- N.J. Workers (Newark Beth Israel) demonstration for contract, 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 55)
  #1428
- St. Clare's Org. Campaign, 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 56)
  #1429
- Summer fun, 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 57)
  #1430
- Frances Goins, 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 58)
  #1431
- Retiree Thomas Bosco, 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 59)
  #1432
- Sickle Cell Screening at Queens General, 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 60)
  #1433
- Retiree Stephen Kearney, 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 61)
  #1434
- Summer fun - Montefiore workers in park, 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 62)
  #1435
- Benefit Plan - Cush family, 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 63)
  #1436
- Retiree Daniel Galauter, 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 64)
  #1437
- Fisherman Jim Tobin - Rx Delegate at Crown Nostrand Ave., 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 65)
  #1438
- Benefit Plan - remedial math class, 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 66)
  #1439
- Kamenkowitz, Phil, 19 July 1971 (Box 52, Folder 67)
  #1440
- Jersey members fishing, July 1971 (Box 52, Folder 68)
  #1441
- Copies IWW songs, July 1971 (Box 52, Folder 69)
  #1442
- Party at Garrich Austin House, 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 70)
  #1443
- Boat ride, 7/1971 (Box 52, Folder 71)
  #1444
- Hospital Corp. demonstration, 8/1971 (Box 52, Folder 72)
  #1445
- Sarah Newman House Org. Committee, 8/1971 (Box 52, Folder 73)
  #1446
- Camp Thorean, 8/1971 (Box 52, Folder 74)
  #1447
- St. Francis Hosp. Technicians join, 8/1971 (Box 52, Folder 75)
  #1448
- Nite of Stars for Angela Davis, 20 Aug. 1971: Ruby Dee, Howard DaSilva, Micki Grant, Patti Jo, Eugene McDaniels, Irene Reid, Saundra Sharp, Jimmy Radcliffe, Irwin C. Watson (Box 52, Folder 76)
  #1449
- Retiree's hear rent control committee Altman, 8/1971 (Box 52, Folder 77)
  #1450
- Movie-making at Homer, 8/1971 (Box 52, Folder 78)
  #1451
- Wilfred-Alexander Lewis, 9/1971 (Box 52, Folder 79)
  #1452
- Furniture Workers Demonstration, 9/1971 (Box 52, Folder 80)
  #1453
- Retirees Welfare Comm. At work, 9/1971 (Box 52, Folder 81)
  #1454
- Training fund LPN Grads, 9/1971 (Box 52, Folder 82)
  #1455
- Miners visit, 9/1971 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  #1456
- Bx-Lebanon Hosp. Community Advisory Bd. - 1199er Anibal Garcia a member, 9/1971 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  #1457
- Jimmy Soto, Jewish Home Grievance, 9/1971 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  #1458
- Jt. Del. Assembly vote, 9/15/1971 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  #1459
- Jones, Clarence: Talk on Attica, 24 Sept.. 1971 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  #1460
- Harlem Artists show opens at Gallery 1199, 9/30/1971 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  #1461
- Demonstration at Federal Plaza against Nixon wage freeze, 1 October 1971 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  #1462
- Demonstration at Federal Plaza against Nixon wage freeze, 1 October 1971 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  #1462 (cont.)
- Art show entries-block artist, 10/1971 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  #1463
- Jones, Clarence at Hosp. D.A. on Attica, 10/1971 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  #1464
- McGovern visits with Davis, 10/1971 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  #1465
- Muskie visit with Davis, 10/1971 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  #1466
- New Democratic Coalition (Leon J. Davis speaking at), 6 October 1971 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  #1467
- Mario Sprouse group in rehearsal, 10/1971 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  #1468
- Philly negotiations (Box 53, Folder 15)
  #1469